# **Personal Info**

#### **Name**

Fábio Ferreira

#### **Phone Number**

927671290

#### Location

Santarém, Portugal

#### **Email**

fabio.f.dev@gmail.com

## **Socials**

#### LinkedIn

https://linkedin.com/in/fabio--ferreira

#### **GitHub**

https://github.com/fabio-m-ferreira

# **My Portfolio**

#### **Website Link**

https://fabio-ferreira.vercel.app

# Soft Skills

- Teamwork
- Problem Solving
- Emotional Intelligence
- Organization
- Adaptability

## Languages

Portuguese Native

English Very good

# Fábio Ferreira

Fullstack Web Developer

#### **Summary**

I'm a Fullstack Developer with a focus on Frontend. Guided by a foundation in design and a career in cybersecurity, I create web solutions that prioritize both aesthetics and resilience. With 4 years of professional experience and more than 6 years coding.

For a more detailed view of my work(tech used and other details), visit my portfolio at https://fabio-ferreira.vercel.app

# **Professional Experience**

# Fullstack Developer | Security Consultant 2022 - Present Layer8 | Cybersecurity company

- Lead developer for the company's component library, ensuring consistency and scalability across all projects.
- Lead developer for a cloud management project that centralizes the company's services, integrating features like user management and service management.
- Contributed significantly to redesigning and restructuring projects to align with the new design guidelines and component library, enabling better adoption across all platforms.

Freelancer 2021 - Present

- Redesigned existing websites to improve usability, aesthetics, and performance, creating a stronger online presence for clients.
- Delivered various creative solutions, including graphic design and multimedia projects, ensuring a cohesive and polished result for every task.

# Front-End Developer | Programmer Assistant Gestix | Invoicing company

2021

- Rebuilt and redesigned the company's main website.
- Developed a customizable, UI/UX-friendly website template for clients.
- Redesigned the backoffice interface to improve usability and customer satisfaction.

### **Personal Info**

#### Name

Fábio Ferreira

#### **Phone Number**

927671290

#### Location

Santarém, Portugal

#### **Email**

fabio.f.dev@gmail.com

## **Socials**

#### LinkedIn

https://linkedin.com/in/fabio--ferreira

#### **GitHub**

https://github.com/ fabio-m-ferreira

# **My Portfolio**

#### **Website Link**

https://fabio-ferreira.vercel.app

# **Soft Skills**

- Teamwork
- Problem Solving
- Emotional Intelligence
- Organization
- Adaptability

## Languages

Portuguese

English Very good

Native

### **Technical Skills**

- Front-end Development: Typescript, React, NextJS, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Storybook, MaterialUI
- Back-end Development: NodeJS, ExpressJS, PHP, MySQL, Firebase
- Other Tools: Figma, Git, GitLab, Github, Docker, Vitest, Jira, SonarQube

## **Education**

# Google UX Professional Certificate

2023

Corsera

Grade: average of 92.19% on all 7 courses

### **Web Development**

2019-2020

ETIC | Escola de Tecnologias Inovação e Criação

• Grade 18/20

## Multimedia Technician - High School

2016 - 2019

Escola Básica e Secundária de Salvaterra de Magos

Grade: 16/20